http://www.martin-eng.com/content/page/681/privacy-policy

Belt Cleaning Solutions
CleanScrape® Primary CleanerCleanScrape® Secondary CleanerPrimary Belt CleanersSecondary Belt CleanersSpecialty Belt CleanersRoll Gen™ System Replacement BladesBelt Cleaner AccessoriesConveyor Belt Safety
Transfer Point Solutions
Roll Gen™ System Belt AlignmentBelt SupportBelt SealingTail ProtectionTransfer Point Safety Accessories
Air Cannon Solutions
Air CannonsSMART™ Series NozzlesFlow Aid AccessoriesRoll Gen™ System
Vibration Solutions
Truck VibratorsElectric VibratorsHydraulic VibratorsRoller VibratorsPiston VibratorsTurbine VibratorsBall VibratorsPortable Pneumatic VibratorsScreen VibratorsRailcar Vibrators
Dust Management and Containment Solutions
Dust FiltrationDust SuppressionDust ContainmentDust Management Safety
Railcar Unloading Solutions
Railcar ConnectorsRailcar OpenersRailcar Vibrators
Safety Solutions
Conveyor Belt SafetyDust Management SafetyMaintenance SafetyMaterial Flow SafetyRailcar Unloading Safety ProductsTransfer Point Safety Accessories
Martin® Process Improvement Services
Walk The Belt™Laser SurveyingSilo Cleaning
Martin® Maintenance & Installation Services
InstallationOngoing MaintenanceMr. Blade® Program
Training and Education
Foundations™ TrainingFoundations™ BookFoundations™ Safety Book
Martin Engineering Company
Our technicians and engineers have been solving bulk material handling problems around the world for over 70 years and are available to provide expert advice and assistance on all of your bulk material handling questions and problems.
Privacy Policy
Martin Engineering Company (“Martin Engineering”) is committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal information private. Because our website (located at the URL http://www.martin-eng.com) includes areas in which individuals can provide personal  information, we have developed Martin Engineering’s Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and practices regarding information we collect about you on this site.
How we gather information about you
Martin Engineering may collect and maintain certain personal information about you when you register at our website. Martin Engineering will use such information internally and may also share a limited amount of your personal information with any subsidiary, affiliate or third-party vendors that act on our behalf, subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Martin Engineering also collects or logs, certain other information that cannot identify you personally when you visit our web site. This information includes your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address and your domain name. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by the ISP through which you access the web and a domain name is the name of the computer itself through which you access the web.
Martin Engineering logs these IP addresses and domain names and aggregates them for system administration and to monitor the use of our site. We use the aggregated information to measure the number of visits to our site, the average time spent on our site, the number of pages viewed and various other site statistics. This monitoring helps us evaluate how our web site is used and continuously improve the content we provide.
Martin Engineering does not purchase or otherwise obtain any supplemental personal information about you from any third parties.
Martin Engineering may disclose personal information about you, without notice, in response to: (i) requests from local, state or federal law enforcement officials; (ii) if requested by any judicial, administrative or similar proceeding or order, such as a subpoena; (iii) or, if otherwise required by law.
One third-party vendor that helps to eliminate spam through our site is Mollum, and their own privacy policy is available for your review.
Opt-in Policy
You will have the opportunity to receive future mailing or permit use of your information for other purposes by "opting-in" by checking one or more opt-in boxes provided on the website. In cases where you opt-in, we use your information to send updates on the categories, products or topics you selected.
Opt-out Policy
If you decide that you do not wish to receive updates on one or more of the categories, products and/or topics selected, please send your request to “opt-out” to Martin Engineering at unsubscribe@martin-eng.com.
Security
We use industry standard efforts to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Some features of the website require the use of a password or access code. You are responsible for protecting the secrecy of your account information and should not share it with any third parties.
Links
The website may contain links to other websites. Martin Engineering is not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or the content of the other websites that are not under its control.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
Martin Engineering reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be preceded by a notice posted to this Privacy Policy at least ten (10) days prior to the effective date of such change.
How to Contact Us
If you have further questions about our website, our products or services, or our privacy policies or practices after reading this Privacy Policy, please contact the Website Administrator.
We're Here to Help
Toll-Free					800-544-2947
Martin EngineeringOne Martin PlaceNeponset, IL 61345-9766Get Directions
info@martin-eng.com
309-852-2384
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
Wait! Consider Our Free Expert Assistance For Any Technical Decisions...
9 out of 10 customers benefit from our expert advice. We highly suggest you take advantage of this Free Assistance to ensure proper product selection and consideration of all components needed to solve your problem. Use the contact options below to get started!
Request Assistance
Find Rep
Find Representative
Call Us Today
800-544-2947
